<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Syllabus on MTH 121</title>
    <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Syllabus on MTH 121</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructor Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/instructor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/instructor/</guid>
      <description>  Michael Casper Instructor
SUNY University at Buffalo
Mathematics Department
Office: 222 Mathematics Building Office Hours: Conducted both online and in-person. See the applicable office hour section of the course handbook for more details. Email: mjcasper@buffalo.edu Contact
    Alex Becerra Teaching Assistant
SUNY University at Buffalo
Mathematics Department
Office: 106 Mathematics Building Office Hours: Mondays 4-5pm and Fridays 3-4pm Email: ajbecerr@buffalo.edu Contact
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/information/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites  MTH 115, ULC 148, or NYS Regents Course B required for registration. ALEKS - Only students who have passed ALEKS with a score of 61 or better are eligible to complete this course (this restriction only applies to the Fall and Spring Semesters).  Delivery Mode This is an online course with in-person exams.
Required Hardware  Textbook - L. Goldstein, D. Schneider, D. Lay, and N. Asmar, Calculus and Its Applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessments</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/assessments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/assessments/</guid>
      <description>Overview Your final grade will be determined by your performance on the following assessments: Homework Assignments, the Exam Registration Form, Midterm Exams, and the Cumulative Final Exam.
Homework On average, there will be approximately 2-4 problem sets assigned each week. They will be posted on our course website each Tuesday and due the following Tuesday at 11:59pm ET. Your grade for each individual homework set will be calculated as the percentage of your correct answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grading</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/grading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/grading/</guid>
      <description>Your Course Average Your final average will be found by averaging your grades with the following weights:
   Assessment Weight     Exam Registration Form 2%    Homework 23%    Highest Midterm Exam 25%    2nd Highest Midterm Exam 25%    3rd Highest Midterm Exam 0%    Cumulative Final Exam 25%     Your Letter Grade Your final letter grade will be determined from your final average by applying the cutoffs:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/schedule/</guid>
      <description>There are 3 types of dates on our class calendar: Lecture, Exam, and Administrative.
Lecture Dates On each scheduled lecture date, there will be three items of business:
 The new Lectures &amp;amp; Homework for that week will be posted by 8:00am ET. The old Lectures &amp;amp; Homework from the previous week are due by 11:59pm ET. Recitation will be held at 1-1:50pm (Eastern Time)  The lecture dates represent the recommended pacing of the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/calendar/</guid>
      <description>August    Date Event Type Description     Aug 27 (Tue)  Lecture Date 1 Sections 0.1, 0.2, 0.3, 0.4 &amp;amp; Recitation No Lectures &amp;amp; HW are due.    September    Date Event Type Description     Sep 3 (Tue)  Lecture Date 2 Sections 0.5, 1.1, 1.2, 1.3 &amp;amp; Recitation No Lectures &amp;amp; HW are formally due.   Sep 6 (Fri)  Exam Date 0 Exam Reg Form Due at 11:59pm ET   Sep 10 (Tue)  Lecture Date 3 Sections 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Policies</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/policies/</guid>
      <description>Academic Integrity Students must be familiar with and abide by the university’s policies and procedures on Academic Integrity. Any violation of this policy will be pursued to the fullest extent of university policy.
Attendance Policy   Technological Attendance: We will be using UBlearns and UBmail (email) for all official course communications. It is required that you check both of these platforms daily.
  Lecture Attendance: You are expected to watch all assigned lecture videos in their entirety by the assigned lecture date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/additional/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/additional/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility Resources If you have any disability which requires reasonable accommodations to enable you to participate in this course, please contact the Office of Accessibility Resources in 60 Capen Hall, 716-645-2608 and also the instructor of this course during the first week of class. The office will provide you with information and review appropriate arrangements for reasonable accommodations.
Changes to the Syllabus This syllabus is subject to amendments as needed. Changes will be announced to the class electronically via email and posted on the course UBlearns page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/syllabus/outcomes/</guid>
      <description>Unit 1 The following learning outcomes will be assessed in the Homework, Midterm Exam #1, and Final Exam:
 Recognize linear, polynomial, rational, and power functions, understand their basic properties and know how to evaluate them. Compute zeros of quadratic functions. Compute limits of algebraic functions graphically, numerically, and algebraically. Interpret the derivative graphically as the slope of the tangent to the graph of a function and algebraically as the limit of difference quotients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>