<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Course Handbook on MTH 141</title>
    <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Course Handbook on MTH 141</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Overview Welcome to the online section of MTH 141 College Calculus 1. We begin by giving a brief overview of the course structure and will then expand on these descriptions later in this handbook. Make sure you carefully read through both the entire course handbook and syllabus and if you still have any questions, contact your instructor immediately.
Essentially, the course consists of five main components: lectures, recitations, office hours, homework assignments, and exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Succeed</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/succeed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/succeed/</guid>
      <description>Time Management Time management skills are essential in successfully completing this course. On average, expect to spend approximately 15+ hours per week on work for this class (lectures, assignments, studying, reading, etc.). Please understand that a lot of responsibility will fall onto your shoulders to work through the material at the pace described in this website. Any online course demands a large degree of dedication and autonomous study habits from the individual student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/homework/</guid>
      <description>Overview The best way to learn mathematics is by practicing it for yourself. Homework will consist of both graded and ungraded problems.
Graded Homework  Graded Homework The graded homework sets for each lecture will be completed online using WeBWork. In general, they are due every Lecture Date (Tuesday) at 11:59pm ET. See the course schedule for more information.
 Login Information:  Select course: 2019_8_MTH141_Casper or use the above button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recitation</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/recitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/recitation/</guid>
      <description>Overview Recitations are conducted as an online video conference, and are an opportunity to engage directly with the teaching assistant by asking questions, working through homework problems together, and reviewing lecture material - all in real time.
Recitations will be held at scheduled times, but will also be recorded and posted in the Recitation Archive for later viewing. We will be using the video conferencing software Zoom which requires a very quick download the first time you attend (and is free for you to use).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours (online)</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Online Office Hours are conducted through a discussion board. The discussion board is an opportunity to engage with the instructor, teaching assistant, and other students by asking and answering questions in a text based format. We will be using the website Piazza for our course Discussion Board. It will require a very quick initial registration and is free to use.
We encourage you to post your questions during normal business hours (9-5pm ET) as these are the times we will be most active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours (in-person)</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours_in_person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours_in_person/</guid>
      <description>Overview The In-Person Office Hours are conducted much like a small-group recitation. Essentially these are in-person meetings with the instructor (and other students) held on a recurring, weekly basis at scheduled times.
How To Participate Please email Prof. Casper if you would like to reserve your spot for one of the time slots listed below. Click the appropriate sign-up link to generate the email.
You can register for either a one-time meeting or a recurring, weekly meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam Registration</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/exam_reg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/exam_reg/</guid>
      <description>Overview Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campus testing center. If you are interested in taking your exams off-campus, we have a list of resources to help you locate a testing center.
The exam registration form is how you communicate to the instructor where you will be taking each of your exams. It is extremely important that you fill this out correctly and by the deadline, regardless of where you are planning on taking the exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locating a Test Site</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/testing/</guid>
      <description>Resources Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campus testing center.
To help locate an off-campus test site we have a few recommended resources:
 Our list of past test sites in New York State National College Testing Association (NCTA) SUNY Exam Proctoring System  These are only recommendations meant to give you a starting point in your search; you are free to use other testing centers not listed in these resources as long as they satisfy the conditions described in the Exam Location Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/getting_help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/getting_help/</guid>
      <description>Content Questions All content related questions about the material or the course should be asked either through the discussion board or during recitation. Most questions that we receive fall under this category - so most likely this is where you should turn.
  Online Office Hours - Conducted through our course discussion board. Enroll by following the instructions described in the syllabus.
  In-Person Office Hours - Weekly, recurring, small-group meetings with the instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>If you are having difficulty viewing the lecture videos, try the following:
 Check your internet connection. Videos might take longer to load on a slow connection. Give the video extra time to load once you select play. Make sure you are using the latest version of your internet browser: Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc&amp;hellip; Some older versions of Chrome have been known to cause issues. Close all open programs, browser windows, browser tabs besides the one window needed for the video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>