<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MTH 141</title>
    <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MTH 141</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructor Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/instructor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/instructor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/overview/</guid>
      <description>How to Study   Start early! Remember, you should be staying on pace with the lecture schedule. It will not be a fun experience if you wait until a day or so before the exam to start your work.
  Review your Online Homework problems. As you complete the homework problems, write down your full solutions with explanations in a neat, organized notebook. This way when exam time comes, you have a nice solutions manual, you created yourself - that you can then refer back to if you get stuck on a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Overview Welcome to the online section of MTH 141 College Calculus 1. We begin by giving a brief overview of the course structure and will then expand on these descriptions later in this handbook. Make sure you carefully read through both the entire course handbook and syllabus and if you still have any questions, contact your instructor immediately.
Essentially, the course consists of five main components: lectures, recitations, office hours, homework assignments, and exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/information/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites  MTH 115, ULC 148, or NYS Regents Course B required for registration. ALEKS - Only students who have passed ALEKS with a score of 76 or better are eligible to complete this course (this restriction only applies to the Fall and Spring Semesters).  Delivery Mode This is an online course with in-person exams.
Required Hardware  Textbook - J. Stewart, Calculus: Early Transcendental Single Variable.  The 8th custom UB edition is the official version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 1 Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam1/</guid>
      <description>Logistics  Date: Thursday, September 26, 2019  Time: 8:45pm-10:15pm ET - (it is a 1.5 hour exam)
 Location: Your exam location is posted on UBlearns.
 What to Bring: You should bring multiple pens / pencils, your approved calculator, and a photo ID.
 Calculator: You are allowed to use only the Texas Instruments TI-30XIIS calculator on the exam. All other calculators are prohibited. See the Calculator and Reference Policy in the syllabus for more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Succeed</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/succeed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/succeed/</guid>
      <description>Time Management Time management skills are essential in successfully completing this course. On average, expect to spend approximately 15+ hours per week on work for this class (lectures, assignments, studying, reading, etc.). Please understand that a lot of responsibility will fall onto your shoulders to work through the material at the pace described in this website. Any online course demands a large degree of dedication and autonomous study habits from the individual student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the Handbook</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/handbook/</guid>
      <description>1a Step 1a   Step 1a: Read the Course Handbook &amp;hellip; all of it!
The Course Handbook gives a detailed explanation of the course structure, all of the resources and instructional material available to you during the course, and instructions on how to access everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeks 1-4</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks1_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks1_4/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, August 27    Recitation: Join me today at 2-2:50pm ETfor our first live online recitation as we discuss the course, look over the syllabus, and answer any questions that you may have. Use the link on the recitation page of the Course Handbook to join the meeting.       Tuesday, September 3    We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET       Tuesday, September 10    We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET       Tuesday, September 17   Recitation  We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET  Section 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeks 5-8</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks5_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks5_8/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, September 24    We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET       Thursday, September 26   Exam 1 is scheduled for today at 8:45pm-10:15pm ET (it is a 1.5 hour exam). A summary of your instructor-approved exam locations is posted on UBlearns under &amp;ldquo;Your Grades and Exam Arrangements&amp;rdquo;.
     Tuesday, October 1    We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET  Section 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessments</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/assessments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/assessments/</guid>
      <description>Overview Your final grade will be determined by your performance on the following assessments: Homework Assignments, the Exam Registration Form, Midterm Exams, and the Cumulative Final Exam.
Homework On average, there will be approximately 2-4 problem sets assigned each week. They will be posted on our course website each Tuesday and due the following Tuesday at 11:59pm ET. Your grade for each individual homework set will be calculated as the percentage of your correct answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 2 Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam2/</guid>
      <description>Logistics  Date: Thursday, October 24, 2019  Time: 8:45pm-10:15pm ET - (it is a 1.5 hour exam)
 Location: Your exam location is posted on UBlearns.
 What to Bring: You should bring multiple pens / pencils, your approved calculator, and a photo ID.
 Calculator: You are allowed to use only the Texas Instruments TI-30XIIS calculator on the exam. All other calculators are prohibited. See the Calculator and Reference Policy in the syllabus for more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/homework/</guid>
      <description>Overview The best way to learn mathematics is by practicing it for yourself. Homework will consist of both graded and ungraded problems.
Graded Homework  Graded Homework The graded homework sets for each lecture will be completed online using WeBWork. In general, they are due every Lecture Date (Tuesday) at 11:59pm ET. See the course schedule for more information.
 Login Information:  Select course: 2019_8_MTH141_Casper or use the above button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>1b Step 1b   Step 1b: Read the Course Syllabus &amp;hellip; all of this as well!
The syllabus gives a detailed explanation of course policies, assessments, grading methods, learning outcomes, and important dates. If you have a question about grades &amp;hellip; the answer is most likely here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeks 9-12</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks9_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks9_12/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, October 22   Recitation We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET
Lectures Below are the two lectures assigned for this week.
Additional Resources and Review Material (optional) Section 4.1: Below is the lecture we use to introduce the concepts of Maximum and Minimum in another course. This may be a helpful resource, if you find yourself struggling with this section.
     Thursday, October 24   Exam 2 is scheduled for today at 8:45pm-10:15pm ET (it is a 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam 3 Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/exam_preparation/exam3/</guid>
      <description>Logistics  Date: Thursday, November 21, 2019  Time: 8:45pm-10:15pm ET - (it is a 1.5 hour exam)
 Location: Your exam location is posted on UBlearns.
 What to Bring: You should bring multiple pens / pencils, your approved calculator, and a photo ID.
 Calculator: You are allowed to use only the Texas Instruments TI-30XIIS calculator on the exam. All other calculators are prohibited. See the Calculator and Reference Policy in the syllabus for more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exams</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/exam/</guid>
      <description>2 Step 2   Step 2: Schedule your exams by following the instructions on the Exam Registration page.
Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campus testing center. The exam registration form is how you communicate to the instructor where you will be taking each of your exams. It is extremely important that you fill this out correctly and by the deadline, regardless of where you are planning on taking the exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grading</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/grading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/grading/</guid>
      <description>Your Course Average Your final average will be found by averaging your grades with the following weights:
   Assessment Weight     Exam Registration Form 2%    Homework 23%    Highest Midterm Exam 25%    2nd Highest Midterm Exam 25%    3rd Highest Midterm Exam 0%    Cumulative Final Exam 25%     Your Letter Grade Your final letter grade will be determined from your final average by applying the cutoffs:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recitation</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/recitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/recitation/</guid>
      <description>Overview Recitations are conducted as an online video conference, and are an opportunity to engage directly with the teaching assistant by asking questions, working through homework problems together, and reviewing lecture material - all in real time.
Recitations will be held at scheduled times, but will also be recorded and posted in the Recitation Archive for later viewing. We will be using the video conferencing software Zoom which requires a very quick download the first time you attend (and is free for you to use).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeks 13-16</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks13_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/lessons/weeks13_16/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, November 19   Recitation We have recitation scheduled for today at 2-2:50pm ET
Lectures Below are the three lectures assigned for this week, all due on December 3rd.
     Thursday, November 21   Exam 3 is scheduled for today at 8:45pm-10:15pm ET (it is a 1.5 hour exam). A summary of your instructor-approved exam locations is posted on UBlearns under &amp;ldquo;Your Grades and Exam Arrangements&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed any typos or technical issues in the lectures, notes or website? Do you have any suggestions for things you think we should be doing? Things that you like? Things that could be better? Let us know!
Feedback Form  This feedback form should not be used to ask for help in the course - that is what the discussion board and recitations are there for!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/homework/</guid>
      <description>3 Step 3   Step 3: Enroll in our online homework system.
The graded homework sets for each lecture will be completed online using WeBWork. Follow the instructions in the Course Handbook and verify that you have access to the system. Let me know immediately if you have any difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/discussion/</guid>
      <description>4 Step 4   Step 4: Enroll in our course discussion board.
This is how we will be conducting our online office hours this semester. It&#39;s also a really good way to get help if you are stuck on anything! Again, follow the instructions in the handbook to enroll.
You can also register for our recurring, weekly in-person office hours. These will be conducted much like a small-group recitation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours (online)</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Online Office Hours are conducted through a discussion board. The discussion board is an opportunity to engage with the instructor, teaching assistant, and other students by asking and answering questions in a text based format. We will be using the website Piazza for our course Discussion Board. It will require a very quick initial registration and is free to use.
We encourage you to post your questions during normal business hours (9-5pm ET) as these are the times we will be most active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/schedule/</guid>
      <description>There are 3 types of dates on our class calendar: Lecture, Exam, and Administrative.
Lecture Dates On each scheduled lecture date, there will be three items of business:
 The new Lectures and Homework for that week will be posted by 8:00am ET. The old Lectures and Homework from the previous week are due by 11:59pm ET. Recitation will be held at 2-2:50pm (Eastern Time)  The lecture dates represent the recommended pacing of the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/calendar/</guid>
      <description>August    Date Event Type Description     Aug 27 (Tue)  Lecture Date 1 Sections 2.1, 2.2 &amp;amp; Recitation No Lectures &amp;amp; HW are due.    September    Date Event Type Description     Sep 3 (Tue)  Lecture Date 2 Sections 2.3, 2.5 &amp;amp; Recitation No Lectures &amp;amp; HW are formally due.   Sep 6 (Fri)  Exam Date 0 Exam Reg Form Due at 11:59pm ET   Sep 10 (Tue)  Lecture Date 3 Sections 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours (in-person)</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours_in_person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/office_hours_in_person/</guid>
      <description>Overview The In-Person Office Hours are conducted much like a small-group recitation. Essentially these are in-person meetings with the instructor (and other students) held on a recurring, weekly basis at scheduled times.
How To Participate Please email Prof. Casper if you would like to reserve your spot for one of the time slots listed below. Click the appropriate sign-up link to generate the email.
You can register for either a one-timemeeting or a recurring, weekly meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recitation</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/recitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/recitation/</guid>
      <description>5 Step 5   Step 5: Read through the recitation page in the Course Handbook; this is where you will go to attend each of our online recitations.
The recitations are also another really good way to get help in this course! Again, follow the instructions in the handbook for how to view both the live and previously recorded recitations.
Join me for our first live online recitation  Tuesday, August 27, 2019 at&amp;nbsp;2-2:50pm&amp;nbsp;ET as we discuss the course, look over the syllabus, and answer any questions that you may have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Policies</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/policies/</guid>
      <description>Academic Integrity Students must be familiar with and abide by the university’s policies and procedures on Academic Integrity. Any violation of this policy will be pursued to the fullest extent of university policy.
Attendance Policy   Technological Attendance: We will be using UBlearns and UBmail (email) for all official course communications. It is required that you check both of these platforms daily.
  Lecture Attendance: You are expected to watch all assigned lecture videos in their entirety by the assigned lecture date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam Registration</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/exam_reg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/exam_reg/</guid>
      <description>Overview Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campustesting center. If you are interested in taking your exams off-campus, we have a list of resources to help you locate a testing center.
The exam registration form is how you communicate to the instructor where you will be taking each of your exams. It is extremely important that you fill this out correctly and by the deadline, regardless of where you are planning on taking the exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/next/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/getting_started/next/</guid>
      <description>6 Step 6   Step 6: Now you are all set!
Head over to the Lectures and Homework and get started with some Calculus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further Information</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/additional/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/additional/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility Resources If you have any disability which requires reasonable accommodations to enable you to participate in this course, please contact the Office of Accessibility Resources in 60 Capen Hall, 716-645-2608 and also the instructor of this course during the first week of class. The office will provide you with information and review appropriate arrangements for reasonable accommodations.
Changes to the Syllabus This syllabus is subject to amendments as needed. Changes will be announced to the class electronically via email and posted on the course UBlearns page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locating a Test Site</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/testing/</guid>
      <description>Resources Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campus testing center.
To help locate an off-campus test site we have a few recommended resources:
 Our list of past test sites in New York State National College Testing Association (NCTA) SUNY Exam Proctoring System  These are only recommendations meant to give you a starting point in your search; you are free to use other testing centers not listed in these resources as long as they satisfy the conditions described in the Exam Location Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/getting_help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/getting_help/</guid>
      <description>Content Questions All content related questions about the material or the course should be asked either through the discussion board or during recitation. Most questions that we receive fall under this category - so most likely this is where you should turn.
  Online Office Hours - Conducted through our course discussion board. Enroll by following the instructions described in the syllabus.
  In-Person Office Hours - Weekly, recurring, small-group meetings with the instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/syllabus/outcomes/</guid>
      <description>Unit 1 The following learning outcomes will be assessed in the Homework, Midterm Exam #1, and Final Exam:
 Evaluate limits using the definition and using algebraic properties of limits. Evaluate limits of functions at infinity and interpret them as horizontal asymptotes. Define continuity and determine whether or not a function is continuous at a point and on an interval. Define derivative and interpret it as the slope of a tangent to the graph of a function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/141/handbook/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>If you are having difficulty viewing the lecture videos, try the following:
 Check your internet connection. Videos might take longer to load on a slow connection. Give the video extra time to load once you select play. Make sure you are using the latest version of your internet browser: Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc&amp;hellip; Some older versions of Chrome have been known to cause issues. Close all open programs, browser windows, browser tabs besides the one window needed for the video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>