<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on MTH 121</title>
    <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on MTH 121</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the Handbook</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/handbook/</guid>
      <description>1a Step 1a   Step 1a: Read the Course Handbook &amp;hellip; all of it!
The Course Handbook gives a detailed explanation of the course structure, all of the resources and instructional material available to you during the course, and instructions on how to access everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>1b Step 1b   Step 1b: Read the Course Syllabus &amp;hellip; all of this as well!
The syllabus gives a detailed explanation of course policies, assessments, grading methods, learning outcomes, and important dates. If you have a question about grades &amp;hellip; the answer is most likely here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exams</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/exam/</guid>
      <description>2 Step 2   Step 2: Schedule your exams by following the instructions on the Exam Registration page.
Everyone has the option to sit for their exams either at UB or an instructor approved off-campus testing center. The exam registration form is how you communicate to the instructor where you will be taking each of your exams. It is extremely important that you fill this out correctly and by the deadline, regardless of where you are planning on taking the exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/homework/</guid>
      <description>3 Step 3   Step 3: Enroll in our online homework system.
The graded homework sets for each lecture will be completed online using WeBWork. Follow the instructions in the Course Handbook and verify that you have access to the system. Let me know immediately if you have any difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/discussion/</guid>
      <description>4 Step 4   Step 4: Enroll in our course discussion board.
This is how we will be conducting our online office hours this semester. It&#39;s also a really good way to get help if you are stuck on anything! Again, follow the instructions in the handbook to enroll.
You can also register for our recurring, weekly in-person office hours. These will be conducted much like a small-group recitation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recitation</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/recitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/recitation/</guid>
      <description>5 Step 5   Step 5: Read through the recitation page in the Course Handbook; this is where you will go to attend each of our online recitations.
The recitations are also another really good way to get help in this course! Again, follow the instructions in the handbook for how to view both the live and previously recorded recitations.
Join me for our first live online recitation  Tuesday, August 27, 2019 at&amp;nbsp;1-1:50pm&amp;nbsp;ET as we discuss the course, look over the syllabus, and answer any questions that you may have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps</title>
      <link>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/next/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjcasper.org/courses/2019/8/121/getting_started/next/</guid>
      <description>6 Step 6   Step 6: Now you are all set!
Head over to the Lectures and Homework and get started with some Calculus!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>